Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm microfilm Treasurer's Office records, 1916-1949 and undated RL.11720
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm microfilm Treasurer's Office records
1916-1949 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.11720
3.0 Linear Feet
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. It is headquartered in New York. Collection includes correspondence, bills, approvals and releases, lists of stockholders, estimates, wage cards, legal files (lawsuits, judgments, claims), insurance documents and other printed materials. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: General Files; Accounts; Foreign Offices Group Insurance; Former Stock Holders; Lawsuits, claims, judgments, etc.; Old Releases (Lux); Signed estimates; and Talent Payment Department
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. It is headquartered in New York.
Beginning in the 1930s, documents from several JWT departments and functions were microfilmed, including Legal Department, Treasurer's Office, As Broadcast Scripts and Commercials for Radio and Television, Investigations, Publicity Department, Artwork, Consumer Panel, and Radio/Television Department. Documents were microfilmed in no order, and typed and hand-written indices were produced for the microfilms. It is believed that once microfilmed, most of the original documents were destroyed.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm microfilm Treasurer's Office records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1987.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
J. Walter Thompson Company. Account files
J. Walter Thompson Company. International Offices
J. Walter Thompson Company. Legal Department records
J. Walter Thompson Company. Treasurer's Office records
Collection Overview
Collection includes correspondence, bills, approvals and releases, lists of stockholders, estimates, wage cards, legal files (lawsuits, judgments, claims), insurance documents and other printed materials. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising; Advertising agencies -- Management
- General Files, 1916-1944 and undated; 1
  - "Cat and Dog", 1931-1932 (Reel 249)
  - Actress Approvals for Comic Strip Ads--Aileen Pringle, 1932 (Reel 249)
  - Actress Approvals for Comic Strip Ads--Anita Stewart, 1932 (Reel 249)
  - Actress Approvals for Comic Strip Ads--Betty Compson, 1932 (Reel 249)
  - Actress Approvals for Comic Strip Ads--Billie Burke, 1932 (Reel 249)
  - Actress Approvals for Comic Strip Ads--Dorothy Meekaill, 1932 (Reel 249)
  - Actress Approvals for Comic Strip Ads--Irene Rich, 1932 (Reel 249)
  - Actress Approvals for Comic Strip Ads--Laura La Plante, 1932 (Reel 249)
  - Actress Approvals for Comic Strip Ads--Nazimova, 1932 (Reel 249)
  - Advertising Agencies Corporation, 1927-1928 (Reel 86)
  - Allan H. Marshall, 1939 (Reel 86)
  - Anglo & London Paris National Bank, 1923-1928 (Reel 86)
  - Approvals of ads and copy--Actressesses, studios, etc., 1935 (Reel 249)
  - Approvals of ads and copy--Actressesses, studios, etc., 1937 (Reel 249)
  - Approvals of ads and copy--Actressesses, studios, etc., 1938 (Reel 249)
  - Approvals of ads and copy--Actressesses, studios, etc., 1939 (Reel 249)
  - Approvals of ads and copy--Actressesses, studios, etc., 1940 (Reel 249)
  - Approvals of ads and copy--Actressesses, studios, etc., 1941 (Reel 249)
  - Approvals of ads and copy--Dr. John Killian, 1935 (Reel 249)
  - Approvals of ads and copy--Dr. John Killian, 1936 (Reel 249)
  - Approvals of ads and copy--Dr. John Killian, 1937 (Reel 249)
  - Approvals of ads and copy--Dr. John Killian, 1938 (Reel 249)
  - Bridget Morgan, 1939 (Reel 87)
  - Cancelled Bills--Auditing, 1935-1937 (Reel 36)
  - Cancelled Bills--Breed Abbott & Morgan, 1929-1930 Nov.; 1931 Dec.-1939 (Reel 3)
  - Cancelled Bills--Insurance, 1935-1937 (Reel 36)
  - Cancelled Bills--Insurance, 1936-1937 (Reel 78)
  - Cancelled Bills--Rent, 1935-1937 (Reel 36)
  - Census of Business (U.S. Dept. of Commerce), 1936 (Reel 86)
  - Chester Du Close, 1932-1936 (Reel 86)
  - Cigarette Treating Machine, 1932 (Reel 86)
  - Cincinnati Office, 1936 (Reel 86)
  - Clarence Hutchins, 1938-1939 (Reel 86)
  - Committee of Credits and Collections, 1938 (Reel 86)
  - Dr. J. A. Killian, 1933 (Reel 86)
  - Eastern Offices Inc., 1926-1937 (Reel 86)
  - Edward Gardner, 1935-1936 (Reel 86)
  - Edward Gordon, 1932-1938 (Reel 86)
  - Edward Steichen, 1924-1931 (Reel 87)
  - Eric Nice, 1933-1934 (Reel 87)
  - Frank Parker Stockbridge (Simmons contract), undated (Reel 87)
  - Harry Uritsky, 1947-1950 (Reel 420)
  - Ideas and letters (Mr. Wilson's files), 1941 (Reel 248)
  - Illinois--State of Certification of Registration, 1933 (Reel 86)
  - J.P. Parsons, 1919-1935 (Reel 87)
  - Jergens--Use of radio articles, 1937 (Reel 86)
  - Jewett-Kennon, 1930-1932 (Reel 86)
  - John Cherry (Sao Paulo), 1935-1936 (Reel 86)
  - John Maloy, 1931-1933 (Reel 86)
  - JWT attendance record, 1938-1940 (Reel 82)
  - JWT Board of Directors Meetings, 1916-1938 (Reel 85)
  - JWT Executive Committee Meetings, 1921-1924 (Reel 85)
  - JWT personnel, 1939-1942 (Reel 248)
  - JWT Stockholders Meetings, 1916-1938 (Reel 85)
  - Kenneth Swanson, 1930-1932 (Reel 87)
  - Kenneth Watson, 1939-1940 (Reel 87)
  - Kilowatt-Reddy (Ashton Collins), 1937-1938 (Reel 86)
  - Louis Joseph Vance, 1933 (Reel 87)
  - Lukis, Stewart & Co.--Bonding, 1940 (Reel 248)
  - Lux Group (Mr. Hinks), 1937 (Reel 249)
  - Mission Dry Corporation, 1935 (Reel 86)
  - New York City proposed Bureau of Drugs and Cosmetics, 1935 (Reel 87)
  - New York City sales tax, 1935 (Reel 87)
  - New York State--Dept. of State, 1934 (Reel 87)
  - Norman Beasley, 1933-1934 (Reel 86)
  - Norman Bel Geddes (architect, lecture hall), 1928 (Reel 86)
  - Norman Coe, 1937-1939 (Reel 86)
  - O.J. Pardee, 1931-1932 (Reel 87)
  - O'Cedar, 1926-1933 (Reel 87)
  - Outside ideas for Lever Brothers, 1937 (Reel 248)
  - Outside ideas for Old Gold cigarettes, 1941-1944 (Reel 248)
  - Outside ideas for radio, 1940-1944 (Reel 248)
  - Paul Cherington, 1931 (Reel 86)
  - Periodical Publishers Association, 1931-1935 (Reel 87)
  - Photographic studio, 1930-1932 (Reel 87)
  - Population and Its Distribution, 1921-1937 (Reel 87)
  - Radio--ASCAP, 1939-1943 (Reel 248)
  - Releases secured in connection with 3-Year Plan, 1933 (Reel 249)
  - Rowland Wood, 1927 (Reel 87)
  - Samuel Krisky, 1937 (Reel 86)
  - Screen star lists, 1931-1932 (Reel 249)
  - Stage star lists, 1931-1932 (Reel 249)
  - Tax case: Personal Service Corporation, 1918-1923 (Reel 67)
  - Tax case: Personal Service Corporation, 1918-1923 (Reel 70)
  - Tax correspondence, 1917-1929 (Reel 67)
  - Tax--Massachusetts, 1930-1932 (Reel 86)
  - Todd & Brown (brass in lecture hall), 1928-1930 (Reel 87)
  - Tower Magazines, 1935-1940 (Reel 87)
  - Vacations, 1928-1940 (Reel 87)
  - Victor Barcas (European Advertising), 1926-1930 (Reel 86)
  - Vincent Gilcher, 1931 (Reel 86)
  - W.L. Day, 1924 (Reel 86)
  - William Schurz, 1931-1933 (Reel 87)
- Accounts--Active, Inactive and Discontinued, 1921-1944 and undated; 2
  - A. & M. Karageusian, undated (Reel 75)
  - A. & M. Karagheusian, undated (Reel 87)
  - A.C. Krumm & Son, undated (Reel 75)
  - A.C. Krumm & Son, undated (Reel 87)
  - Albert E. Peirce & Co. (Chicago), undated (Reel 76)
  - Albert E. Peirce & Co. (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - Amalgamated Textiles, undated (Reel 73)
  - American Appraisal (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - American British Improvement Corporation, undated (Reel 73)
  - American British Improvement Corporation, undated (Reel 86)
  - American British Improvement Corporation, undated (Reel 87)
  - American British Improvement Corporation, undated (Reel 88)
  - American Crayon (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - American Enka, undated (Reel 73)
  - American Hair Felt (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - American Map (Toledo Scale), 1931-1932 (Reel 86)
  - American Social Surveys, 1940-1943 (Reel 535)
  - American Tobacco, undated (Reel 73)
  - American Writing Paper, undated (Reel 73)
  - Anderson Motor, undated (Reel 73)
  - Andrew Jergens, undated (Reel 75)
  - Apple presentation, 1936 (Reel 536)
  - Arbuckle Brothers, undated (Reel 73)
  - Art Loom, undated (Reel 87)
  - Artloom, undated (Reel 73)
  - Associated Corn Products (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - Associated Tile Manufacturers, undated (Reel 73)
  - Association of Pacific Fisheries--Canned Salmon Industry, 1935-1941 (Reel 535)
  - Atlantic Coast Fisheries, 1929-1931 (Reel 536)
  - Atlantic Coast Fisheries, undated (Reel 87)
  - Aunt Jemima (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - Aunt Jemima (Chicago), undated (Reel 76)
  - Aunt Jemima (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - Australian News and Informatin Bureau, 1941-1942 (Reel 536)
  - B.F. Goodrich Rubber, undated (Reel 74)
  - Baldwin Laboratories, undated (Reel 73)
  - Ballard & Ballard, undated (Reel 73)
  - Banner Cigar (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - Beller & Co., undated (Reel 73)
  - Berlin Mills, undated (Reel 73)
  - Bireley's (Blyth) (San Francisco), undated (Reel 73)
  - Bishop & Babcock (Cleveland), undated (Reel 73)
  - Bishopric Manufacturing (Cincinnati), undated (Reel 73)
  - British Columbia Packers, undated (Reel 87)
  - Brunswick-Balke-Callender (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - Buckeye Soda Products (Cincinnati), undated (Reel 73)
  - Buckingham & Hecht (San Francisco), undated (Reel 73)
  - Burry Biscuit, 1936-1937 (Reel 536)
  - Burry Biscuit, undated (Reel 87)
  - Butterick Publishing, undated (Reel 73)
  - C.W. Breneman, undated (Reel 73)
  - California Fresh Bartlett Advisory Board, 1937-1940 (Reel 535)
  - Carling Breweries (Toronto), undated (Reel 73)
  - CeCo Manufacturing, undated (Reel 73)
  - Ceco: Receipt of Morton Milman, undated (Reel 536)
  - Celotex (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - Central Bank of Oakland (San Francisco), undated (Reel 73)
  - Central Bank of Oakland (San Francisco), undated (Reel 87)
  - Central Public Service Corp. (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - Charles D. Barney, undated (Reel 73)
  - Charles Williams Stores, undated (Reel 50)
  - Char-Tex (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - Chase and Sanborn: Major Bowes Amateur Hour, 1935 (Reel 535)
  - Chatham Manufacturing, undated (Reel 73)
  - Chauncey Jerome, undated (Reel 73)
  - Cheek-Neal Coffee, undated (Reel 73)
  - Chelmsford Ginger Ale (Boston), undated (Reel 73)
  - Chicago Evening American (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - Chicago Evening American (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - Chicago, Burlington & Quincy Rail Road, undated (Reel 73)
  - Christian Herald, undated (Reel 73)
  - Cinecolor, 1939-1941 (Reel 535)
  - City Baking, 1923-1931 (Reel 535)
  - Club Aluminum (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - Coast Fishing (Los Angeles), undated (Reel 73)
  - Coast Fishing (Los Angeles), undated (Reel 87)
  - Coca-Cola Bottling Co. of Los Angeles, 1936 (Reel 535)
  - Cohen & Lang, undated (Reel 73)
  - Collegiate World Publishing (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - Colonial Air Transport, undated (Reel 73)
  - Colonial Airways, undated (Reel 73)
  - Cooper's (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - Corn Products Refining, undated (Reel 87)
  - Corning Glass Works, undated (Reel 73)
  - Corning Glass Works, undated (Reel 87)
  - Corticelli Silk, undated (Reel 73)
  - Cosmopolitan, undated (Reel 87)
  - Cox Confectionery (Boston), undated (Reel 73)
  - Cream of Wheat, undated (Reel 80)
  - Cream of Wheat, undated (Reel 87)
  - Crosley Radio (Cincinnati), undated (Reel 73)
  - Crown Products (San Francisco), undated (Reel 73)
  - Crown Products (San Francisco), undated (Reel 87)
  - Curtis Flying Service, undated (Reel 73)
  - Curtis Publishing, undated (Reel 73)
  - Curtiss Candy, 1930-1931, 1940 (Reel 536)
  - Curtiss Candy (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - Curtiss Candy (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - Davey Tree Experts (Chicago), undated (Reel 73)
  - Davey Tree Experts (Chicago), undated (Reel 74)
  - Davison Chemical (Sylox), undated (Reel 74)
  - Delray (San Francisco), undated (Reel 74)
  - Delray (San Francisco), undated (Reel 87)
  - Deltor-Butterick Patterns, undated (Reel 74)
  - Deppe Motors, undated (Reel 74)
  - Detmer, Bruner & Mason, undated (Reel 74)
  - Detroit Brewing, undated (Reel 80)
  - Detroit Steering Wheel, undated (Reel 74)
  - Diamond Crystal Salt (Chicago), undated (Reel 74)
  - Distributors Group (New York downtown), undated (Reel 74)
  - Dolly Madison Baking, undated (Reel 74)
  - Douglas0Pectin, undated (Reel 74)
  - Douglass Lighter (San Francisco), undated (Reel 74)
  - Dreicer, undated (Reel 74)
  - Durham Duplex Razor, 1934-1935 (Reel 535)
  - Durham Duplex Razor, undated (Reel 87)
  - Dwight Manufacturing (Boston), undated (Reel 74)
  - E.A. Pierce & Co., undated (Reel 76)
  - E.F. Hauserman (Chicago), undated (Reel 75)
  - Easy Washing Machine, undated (Reel 80)
  - Easy Washing Machine, undated (Reel 87)
  - Eberhard Faber Pencil, undated (Reel 74)
  - Eberhard Faber Pencil, undated (Reel 87)
  - Eccolene (Detroit), undated (Reel 74)
  - Eisendrath Glove (Chicago), undated (Reel 74)
  - Electric Boat, undated (Reel 74)
  - Electric Steel (Chicago), undated (Reel 74)
  - Elizabeth Arden, undated (Reel 73)
  - Elms & Sellon, undated (Reel 74)
  - Emerson Drug, undated (Reel 74)
  - Emery Industries (Cincinnati), undated (Reel 74)
  - Emil Grossman Manufacturing, undated (Reel 74)
  - Erskine-Danforth, undated (Reel 74)
  - Eugene Greenhut, undated (Reel 74)
  - Exchange Trust (Boston), undated (Reel 74)
  - Export Information Bureau, 1941-1944 (Reel 536)
  - F. Schumacher, undated (Reel 77)
  - F. Schumacher, undated (Reel 88)
  - F.A. Smithers & Co., undated (Reel 77)
  - Federated Engineers Development, undated (Reel 74)
  - Felt & Tarrant (Chicago), undated (Reel 74)
  - Ferry Cap & Set Screw, undated (Reel 74)
  - Fidelio Brewery, undated (Reel 74)
  - Fidelio Brewery, undated (Reel 87)
  - Findley Brazil (Cia, Dos Annunois em Bonds), undated (Reel 74)
  - Fleischmann, 1926-1937 (Reel 80)
  - Fleischmann, 1927-1930 (Reel 81)
  - Florida Blend, undated (Reel 74)
  - Foamite-Childs, undated (Reel 74)
  - Foremost Dairy Products, 1930-1935 (Reel 536)
  - Foremost Dairy Products, undated (Reel 87)
  - Fort Worth & Denver City Rail Road, undated (Reel 74)
  - Freihofer Baking, undated (Reel 74)
  - Fulton Foundry & Machine, undated (Reel 74)
  - G. Piel, undated (Reel 76)
  - Gammack & Co. (New York downtown), undated (Reel 74)
  - Gantner & Mattern (San Francisco), undated (Reel 74)
  - Garner & Co., undated (Reel 74)
  - Gates Tours, undated (Reel 74)
  - Geier Co. P.A. (Chicago), undated (Reel 74)
  - General Mills (Chicago), undated (Reel 74)
  - General Motors Export, undated (Reel 87)
  - General Shoe (Chicago), undated (Reel 74)
  - General Timber Service (formerly Weyerhauser Forest Products), undated (Reel 74)
  - George P. Ide & Co., undated (Reel 75)
  - George P. Ide & Co., undated (Reel 87)
  - Gerardine, 1933 (Reel 88)
  - Gillies Aviation, undated (Reel 74)
  - Globe-Wernicke (Cincinnati), undated (Reel 74)
  - Golden Bear Cookie, undated (Reel 74)
  - Goldwyn Pictures, undated (Reel 74)
  - Good Luck Food, undated (Reel 74)
  - Goodrich prepared contracts, 1936 (Reel 535)
  - Gorham, undated (Reel 74)
  - Gorham, undated (Reel 87)
  - Graham-Paige Motors, 1937-1939 (Reel 81)
  - Grape Nuts (London), undated (Reel 74)
  - Griesedieck Western Brewery (St. Louis), undated (Reel 74)
  - Grove Laboratories: Bromo Quinine, 1940-1941 (Reel 535)
  - Gruen Watch Maker's Guild (Cincinnati), undated (Reel 74)
  - Gulbrausen (Chicago), undated (Reel 74)
  - H.P. Hood & Sons, undated (Reel 75)
  - H.P. Hood & Sons, undated (Reel 87)
  - Haasenstein & Vogler, undated (Reel 74)
  - Haasenstein & Vogler, undated (Reel 75)
  - Hal Roach Studios (United Artists), undated (Reel 76)
  - Hal Roach Studios (United Artists), undated (Reel 77)
  - Hales Bedding Stores, undated (Reel 75)
  - Hales Bedding Stores, undated (Reel 87)
  - Hammond Clock, undated (Reel 75)
  - Hammond Clock, undated (Reel 81)
  - Hanovia Chemical and Manufacturing, undated (Reel 75)
  - Hanovia Chemical and Manufacturing, undated (Reel 87)
  - Harris Forbes & Co., undated (Reel 75)
  - Harris-Forbes, undated (Reel 87)
  - Hassler Manufacturing, undated (Reel 75)
  - Hassler Manufacturing, undated (Reel 87)
  - Hathaway Bakeries, undated (Reel 75)
  - Hathaway Bakeries, undated (Reel 87)
  - Hauserman, undated (Reel 87)
  - Hellyer & Co. (Japanese tea), undated (Reel 87)
  - Holland House, undated (Reel 75)
  - Holland House, undated (Reel 128)
  - Hoosier Manufacturing (Chicago), undated (Reel 75)
  - Hoosier Manufacturing (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - Hooven & Allison (Cincinnati), undated (Reel 75)
  - Horlick's Malted Milk (Chicago), undated (Reel 75)
  - Horse Show, 1935-1939 (Reel 535)
  - Hotel Roosevelt, undated (Reel 88)
  - Houbigant, undated (Reel 75)
  - Howell, Douglas & Co., 1938 (Reel 535)
  - Howlett & Hockmeyer, undated (Reel 75)
  - Howlett & Hockmeyer, undated (Reel 87)
  - Illinois Printing & Publishing (Chicago Herald & Examiner), undated (Reel 75)
  - Illinois Printing & Publishing (Chicago Herald & Examiner), undated (Reel 87)
  - Improved Products (see Kari Keen Manufacturing), undated (Reel 75)
  - Independent Grocers Alliance of America, undated (Reel 75)
  - Individual Enterprise Alliance, 1940 (Reel 535)
  - Industrial Alcohol Institute, undated (Reel 87)
  - Initiative (Seattle Office), 1938 (Reel 535)
  - International B.F. Goodrich, undated (Reel 87)
  - International Printing Ink, undated (Reel 87)
  - International Shoe (St. Louis), undated (Reel 75)
  - International Silver, undated (Reel 81)
  - International Telephone and Telegraph, undated (Reel 75)
  - International Telephone and Telegraph, undated (Reel 87)
  - International Vitamin, undated (Reel 75)
  - International Vitamin, undated (Reel 87)
  - Interstate Trap Shooting Association, undated (Reel 87)
  - Iron Mountain (Chicago), undated (Reel 75)
  - Iron Mountain (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - Isuan (San Francisco), undated (Reel 75)
  - Isuan (San Francisco), undated (Reel 87)
  - J.C. Penney, undated (Reel 76)
  - J.P. Stevens, undated (Reel 77)
  - Jackson Piano (Chicago), undated (Reel 75)
  - Jackson Piano (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - Jantzen Knitting Mills, undated (Reel 87)
  - Japanese Tea Growers Association (Chicago), undated (Reel 75)
  - John Jessel, 1941-1942 (Reel 536)
  - Johnson & Johnson, undated (Reel 75)
  - Johnson & Johnson, undated (Reel 87)
  - Johnson Motor, undated (Reel 87)
  - Julian Sale Leather Goods, undated (Reel 75)
  - Julian Sale Leather Goods, undated (Reel 88)
  - Julius Kayser & Co., undated (Reel 75)
  - Kari-Keen Manufacturing, undated (Reel 75)
  - Kari-Keen Manufacturing, undated (Reel 87)
  - Kent-Costikyan Trading Company, undated (Reel 75)
  - Kent-Costikyan Trading Company, undated (Reel 87)
  - Klearflax Linen Looms (Chicago), undated (Reel 75)
  - Klearflax Linen Looms (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - Klein's Rapid Shoe Repair, undated (Reel 87)
  - Kops Brothers, undated (Reel 75)
  - Kops Brothers, undated (Reel 87)
  - Krohn-Fechheimer, undated (Reel 75)
  - L.C. Chase, undated (Reel 73)
  - L.C. Smith & Corona Typewriters, undated (Reel 77)
  - L.C. Smith & Corona Typewriters, undated (Reel 88)
  - La Gerardine, undated (Reel 75)
  - La Gerardine, undated (Reel 87)
  - Lake of the Woods Milling, 1936-1937 (Reel 536)
  - Langendorf United Bakeries (San Francisco), undated (Reel 75)
    Scope and Contents
    Also radio program material used by Rush-Hughes from book "Alaskans All" by Barrett Willoughby
  - Langendorf United Bakeries (San Francisco), undated (Reel 87)
  - Lansdowne (formerly Schweizer Importer), undated (Reel 75)
  - Lehn & Fink, undated (Reel 75)
  - Lehn & Fink, undated (Reel 87)
  - Leslie-California Salt (San Francisco), undated (Reel 75)
  - Leslie-California Salt (San Francisco), undated (Reel 87)
  - Letters of terms, old forms, etc., 1918-1937 (Reel 86)
  - Lewis Manufacturing, undated (Reel 87)
  - Linen Thread Co., undated (Reel 75)
  - Linen Thread Co., undated (Reel 87)
  - Log Cabin Products (Chicago), undated (Reel 75)
  - Log Cabin Products (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - M.C. Shapiro (Los Angeles), undated (Reel 77)
  - M.C. Shapiro (Los Angeles), undated (Reel 88)
  - M.H. & A.E. Margerison (division of West Point Manufacturing), undated (Reel 75)
  - M.J. Meehan (New York downtown), undated (Reel 75)
  - Madison-Kipp (Chicago), undated (Reel 75)
  - Madison-Kipp (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - Magazine of Wall Street (New York downtown), undated (Reel 75)
  - Martini & Rossi, 1939-1941 (Reel 536)
  - Maskakee Salts, undated (Reel 75)
  - Maskakee Salts, undated (Reel 87)
  - Massachusetts Baking, undated (Reel 75)
  - Massachusetts Baking, undated (Reel 87)
  - Mathieson Alkali Works, undated (Reel 75)
  - Mathieson Alkali Works, undated (Reel 87)
  - Matson Navigation (San Francisco), undated (Reel 75)
  - Matthews Engineering (Cleveland), undated (Reel 75)
  - McCall, 1938 (Reel 535)
  - McCall, undated (Reel 75)
  - McCawley & Co., undated (Reel 75)
  - McCawley & Co., undated (Reel 87)
  - McCrory Stores, undated (Reel 75)
  - McCrory Stores, undated (Reel 87)
  - Melville Shoe, undated (Reel 75)
  - Melville Shoe, undated (Reel 87)
  - Meredith Publishing, undated (Reel 75)
  - Meredith Publishing, undated (Reel 87)
  - Michigan Gas and Oil, 1939-1942 (Reel 535)
  - Mickey Malto Products (San Francisco), undated (Reel 75)
  - Mickey Malto Products (San Francisco), undated (Reel 87)
  - Moorman Manufacturing (Chicago), undated (Reel 75)
  - Moorman Manufacturing (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - Morris Mann & Reilly (Chicago), undated (Reel 75)
  - Morris Mann & Reilly (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - Morris Plan Bank of Virginia, undated (Reel 75)
  - Morris Plan Bank of Virginia, undated (Reel 87)
  - Mortgage Bond Company of New York, undated (Reel 75)
  - Motor Improvements, undated (Reel 75)
  - Motor Improvements, undated (Reel 87)
  - Mountain Valley Mineral Water, 1938-1940 (Reel 536)
  - Nac Products, undated (Reel 81)
  - Nac Products, undated (Reel 87)
  - Nash Motor (Chicago), undated (Reel 75)
  - Nash Motor (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - National Baking (St. Louis), undated (Reel 75)
  - National Bureau of Casualty and Surety Underwriters, 1938 (Reel 536)
  - National Cheese Industry, 1942 (Reel 536)
  - National Committee for Music Appreciation, undated (Reel 75)
  - National Dairy Products (Sealtest), undated (Reel 75)
  - National Dehydrators Association, 1942-1943 (Reel 536)
  - National Electrical Manufacturers Association, undated (Reel 87)
  - National Lumber Manufacturers Association, undated (Reel 75)
  - National Paper Products (Chicago), undated (Reel 75)
  - National Paper Products (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - Nestle, undated (Reel 75)
  - Nestle, undated (Reel 87)
  - New England Confectionery, undated (Reel 75)
  - New England Confectionery, undated (Reel 76)
  - New England Confectionery, undated (Reel 87)
  - New Hotel Jefferson (St. Louis), undated (Reel 76)
  - New Jersey Brewers Association, 1938 (Reel 535)
  - New York Dress Institute, 1942 (Reel 535)
  - New York Post, undated (Reel 76)
  - Norfolk-Portsmouth Chamber of Commerce, undated (Reel 76)
  - Norfolk-Portsmouth Chamber of Commerce, undated (Reel 87)
  - North American Co., undated (Reel 76)